[音乐]
[MUSIC]
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：用功能术语描述这一点，对吗？
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Describing this with the func term, right?
所以承诺是一个有价值的函数
So the Promise is a function that has a value
然后我可以在我的-&gt；&gt；扬声器2上访问：你真的是这个意思吗，
that then I can access on my- &gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Do you really mean this,
大写P承诺？
capital P promise?
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：我想是的。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: I think so.
好的，大写的P，Promise是内置在Java脚本中的。
Okay, capital P, Promise is built into Java Script.
它是一个必须用new关键字so调用的构造函数
It is a constructor that has to be called with the new keyword so
这使得它与我们与funcs讨论的任何东西都有很大的不同。
that makes it very different from anything we were talking about with funcs.
你构筑承诺的方式就是通过
The way you construct a Promise is to pass
在一个我称之为Executor的函数中。
in a function which I've called executor here.
这是规范中使用的术语。
That's the terminology used in the spec.
无论你传入的是什么函数
Whatever function you pass in and
无论它叫什么，都将接收到函数回调。
whatever it's called is going to receive to function callbacks.
您可以使用两个实用程序来处理
Two utilities that you can use to handle the resolution of
您的承诺决定履行拒绝。
your Promise resolved for fulfilling reject for rejecting.
&gt；&gt；扬声器3：所以，我只想把这个连接到
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: And so, I'm just want to take this connected to
流，因为在我调用的时候，我在输出端传递，对吗？
the flow, cuz at some point when I call, I pass at output, right?
我的诺言已经兑现了，对吧？
My promise has been returned, right?
当它完成它的工作时它就会知道
It's when it finishes its work it will then know
我已经向它注册了输出，对吗？
that I've registered output to it, right?
然后你会发送，说，好的，
And then you'd send, say, okay,
现在我将执行输出，因为您注册了。
now I'm going to execute output because you registered.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：我认为是-&gt；&gt；扬声器3：函数。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: I think it's- &gt;&gt; Speaker 3: The function to.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：我想也许我想要一个我不确定的困惑，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: I think maybe I want one of the confusions I'm not sure,
但我认为可能部分混淆是因为你试图
but I think maybe part of the confusion here is you're trying to
将整个过程合并为一个心理步骤。
conflate the whole process into one mental step.
这是两个完全不同的问题。
It's two entirely separate concerns.
其中一个问题是如何解决承诺，
One concern is how the Promise gets resolved,
这就是我在第25行展示的，第25行正在解决这个承诺。
that's what I'm showing here on the line 25, line 25 is resolving the Promise.
不要考虑如何解决承诺，
Don't think about how a Promise is resolved,
当你换帽子的时候，想想你对承诺决议的反应。
when you switch hats to think about how you respond to a Promise resolution.
如果你试图同时考虑这些事情，你会感到困惑的。
You're going to get confused if you try to think about those at the same time.
第38行是对承诺决议的响应，并且
Line 38 is a response to a Promise resolution, and
在第38行谁管它是怎么解决的。
on line 38 who the hell cares how it got resolved.
不管怎么解决的。
Doesn't matter how it got resolved.
重要的是，这就是我如何声明对承诺的回应。
All that matters is this is how I'm declaring the response to a Promise.
我建议在你的脑海中把这两个完全分开。
I would recommend keeping those two completely separate in your mind.
因为看起来有些问题是混为一谈的，当人们
Cuz it seems like some of the questions are kind of conflating when people
都在说这是解决值还是其他什么。
are saying is this the resolve value or whatever.
那可能是一些人的困惑，是试图保持那些一步一个脚印。
That might be were some of the confusion, is trying to keep those as one step.
有两个完全独立的功能。
There are two entirely separate capabilities.
顺便说一句，这很重要。
And that's important, by the way.
这是关注点的分离。
That's a separation of concern.
我们应该能够考虑对承诺的反应
We should be able to think about the response to a Promise
完全独立于如何解决承诺。
entirely independently to how a Promise gets resolved.
&gt；&gt；扬声器3：我只想确定我
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: I just want to make sure the thing I
不得不告诉自己只是对正在发生的事情一无所知，就这么做吧。
have to tell myself is just be ignorant of whatever is happening and just do this.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：这绝对不是我想要的。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: That is absolutely not what I want.
&gt；&gt；扬声器3：这就是我想避免的，所以
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: That's what I wanna avoid and so
这就是为什么我要试着去理解。
that's why I'm asking to try to understand.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：我绝对认为这是我所教的一切的对立面
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: I absolutely that is the antithesis of everything I teach
我不想要这个信息是，不理解它。
I do not want the message to be, don't understand it.
我希望消息能够单独理解，所以在这里当我调用Resolve时，
I want the message to be understand it separately so here when I call resolve,
我在告诉诺言，这是一个与诺言相关的神奇功能
I am telling the Promise that's a magical function connected to the Promise I
我在暗地里告诉你的承诺，解决你自己的问题。
am telling the Promise under the covers resolve yourself.
当承诺被告知要自行解决时，它所做的反应就是去
And the response that a Promise does when it is told to resolve itself is to go and
寻找任何已注册的人，然后处理程序和
look for anybody that's registered and then handler and
执行该处理程序并传递其值。
execute that then handler and pass along its values.
这就是如何构建承诺实现的香肠制作。
That's the sausage making of how a Promise implementation is built.
它有一个由Then处理程序组成的内部数组，并在它们之间循环。
It's got an internal array of then handlers and it loops through them.
&gt；&gt；演讲者3：是的，这就是我之前想说的。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Yeah, that's what I was trying to articulate earlier though.
输出是在幕后完成的那组事情中。
The output is in that set of things that is done under the covers to.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：是的，我想也许我到了哪里，我们被弄糊涂了
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Yeah, I think maybe where I got where we were getting confused as
你说输出是结果，不是。
you were saying output is result, it's not.
&gt；&gt；扬声器3：不，是的。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: No, no, no, yeah.
我之前说过，那是-&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：解决火灾
I said that earlier, that was- &gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Resolve fires off
幕后的异步操作
an asynchronous action under the covers
它告诉它查看已注册的处理程序的列表，并
that tells it to go through a list of then handlers that have been registered and
其中一个处理程序将是输出函数。
one of those then handlers is going to be the output function.
它会确保传递信息，好吗？
And it will make sure to pass the message along, okay?
这就是承诺中的所有实现。
That's all implementation inside of a Promise.
还有许诺的图书馆你可以去
And there are Promise libraries that you could go and
阅读符合规范的允许库。
read that are spec compliant Promise libraries.
你可以去看书，看看他们是如何做这些事情的，我建议你这样做。
You can go and read and see how they do those things, and I I recommend that.
我写了Promise库作为我对承诺的理解的一部分。
I wrote Promise libraries as part of my understanding of promises.
&gt；&gt；扬声器4：你会抓住错误吗？
&gt;&gt; Speaker 4: Are you gonna get to catching errors?
有一些问题-&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：我真的不认为
There's some questions that- &gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: I don't really think
我们将非常注意在这个特定点捕获错误。
we're gonna pay much attention to catching errors at this particular point.
&GT；&GT；演讲者4：其中一个问题就是，如果你想在结尾加上一句话，
&gt;&gt; Speaker 4: One of the questions was just, if you would put a catch at the end,
这会捕捉到任何at末端的错误吗？
would that catch errors in any of the at ends?
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：是的，catch是一种速记，好吗？
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Yes, catch is a shorthand, okay?
如果我在这里接球。
If I do a catch here.
它将在此链中的任何位置接收到创建错误的错误消息。
It would receive an error message anywhere in this chain that created an error.
即使我做了什么，我也应该很久以前就把这个拿出来，
Even if I did something, I should have taken this out a long time ago,
这个链中的任何东西，比如我调用一个不存在的函数。
anything in this chain like if I call a doesn't exist function.
这将抛出一个JavaScript错误，因为没有
That's gonna throw a JavaScript error because there is no doesn't
EXIST函数。
exist function.
JavaScript错误将变成拒绝
That JavaScript error is going to turn into of a rejection
回到第43行的承诺。
of the promise that was returned to line 43.
因为第43行不处理，第44行不处理
Because line 43 doesn't handle it and line 44 doesn't handle it and
第47行不处理它，第48行不处理它。
line 47 doesn't handle it and line 48 doesn't handle it.
这种拒绝将沿着链条向下传播
That rejection is going to propagate its way all the way down the chain skipping
所有其他步骤，它最终将在51行被捕获。
all those other steps and it will finally be caught here on line 51.
我们会在这里打印JavaScript异常。
And we'd get the JavaScript exception printed here.
catch与.Then是一回事
The .catch is the same thing as a .then
在那里我们不会把任何东西传递给成功处理者。
where we don't pass anything for the success handler.
所以这两者在功能上是等价的。
So those two are functionally equivalent.
注册错误处理程序的位置和频率是没有硬性规则的
Where and how often you register error handlers is there is no hard and fast rule
为此，它取决于系统的行为，即预期的行为。
for this it's dependent upon the behavior the intended behavior of your system.
例如，如果我在这里注册接球，
If I register to catch right here for example,
然后，一旦捕获到错误，就会发生什么。
then what happens is once a error has been caught.
它完全是try catch的同义词，这意味着它被捕获了并且
It's exactly synonymous to a try catch, which means that it was caught and
它允许链的其余部分照常进行。
it allows the rest of the chain to continue as normal.
因此，如果您希望在承诺链中的某个点从错误中恢复，
So if you want to recover from an error at some point in your Promise chain,
您可以将错误处理放在那里。
you can put an error handling there.
另一方面，如果你的假设是链中任何地方的错误
If on the other hand your assumption is that an error anywhere in the chain
是一种致命的无法恢复的状态，我们需要摆脱一切，
is a fatal unrecoverable condition and we need to fall out of everything,
然后只需在链条的末端或它们的混合物中放置一个捕获物。
then just put a catch at the end of your chain or a mixture they're of.
但是没有硬性的规则来回答这个问题，你必须弄清楚。
But there's no hard and fast rule to answer that just you have to figure out.
它和我告诉你的完全一样，在你的整个身体周围包裹着一个尝试的捕获物
It's exactly the same as me telling you to wrap a try catch around your whole
功能。
function.
或者您是否在函数的每一行周围都扭曲了一个try catch？
Or do you warp a try catch around every single line of your function?
这个问题的答案取决于你。
The answer to that question is up to you.
取决于你想怎么处理它。
And up to how you want to handle it.
&gt；&gt；Speaker 3：和第40行的输入，该值将
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: And the input to line 40 the value would
是捕获的返回值。
be the return value from the catch.
对，catch将返回一个值，然后就是传递给40的值。
Right, catch is gonna return a value and that will then be the value passed to 40.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：错误处理程序可以返回值，该值将成为
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Your error handler can return value that becomes the success for
下一步。
the next step.
我不想进入错误处理的原因是
The reason I didn't want to get into error handling is because
我们进入了复杂问题的整个兔子道。
we get into a whole side rabbit trail of complex issues.
当你更多地玩弄承诺的时候，你会发现这些事情，但是
Those are things you'll discover as you play more with Promises but
我不想让我们偏离轨道，理解这里的整体模式。
I don't want us get too far off track and understanding the overall pattern here.
所以你需要实践承诺
So you're gonna need to practice with promises
我已经详细地写了所有这些东西。
I have written about all of this stuff in detail.
我鼓励你去读我写过的书和博客。
I encourage you to go and read the books and blogs that I've written about.
这些承诺问题和我确实详细介绍了错误处理。
These Promise issues and I do cover error handling in exquisite detail.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：好的，让我们把堆栈弹回原来的位置，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: All right, let's pop the stack back to where we were before,
只是为了确保我们回到了相同的轨道上，p1。然后(Output)。然后返回p2。
just to make sure we're back on the same track, p1 .then(output) .then return p2.
.Then(Output).然后返回p3。
.then(output) .then return p3.
.然后(输出)然后输出完成。
.then(output) then output complete.
这就是这里的规范流控制。
That's the canonical flow control here.
我们把问题解决了吗？
Did we get the questions handled?
&GT；&GT；扬声器4：我想是的，听起来是这样。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 4: I think so, it sounds like it.
我认为最大的事情是他们不明白
I think the biggest thing was that they didn't understand what
Promise API实际是什么样子，以及
the promise API what that actually looked like and
这就是决心的真正来源。
that was where the resolve was actually coming from.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：好的，这个解决方案很好，它有一种优雅。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Okay, this solution is nice, it has an elegance to it.
它是垂直方向的链条而不是嵌套，
It's a vertically oriented chain instead of a nesting,
我跟你说过，有一种东西叫做承诺地狱。
I mentioned to you that there is such a thing as Promise hell.
你应该知道的承诺地狱的表达之一，
And one of the expressions of Promise hell that you should be aware of,
这就是我之前所说的不把问题混为一谈的原因。
it's kind of what I was getting at earlier about not conflating concerns.
思考这个允诺链的另一种方式是说这样的话
Another way of thinking about this Promise chain is to say something like
我将调用文本的输出函数。
I'm going to call the output function for text.
然后我会打电话给p2.then&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：然后
And then I'm going to call p2.then &gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: And
在该函数内部，我将输出文本，然后p3。
inside of that function I'm going to output the text and then p3.then.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：我将输出文本和
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: And I'm going to output the text and
输出完成。
output complete.
如果没有额外的花括号和右括号，
Without me putting in the extra curly brace and closing parentheses,
这是表达流量控制的一种完全有效的方式，
that's a completely valid way of expressing the flow control,
它将有完全相同的最终结果。
it will have the exact same end result.
这是一种不好的风格，这是一种不好的成语，而且
This is a bad style, this is a bad idiom, and
这是人们谈论诺言地狱时的表达之一。
this is one of the expressions when people talk about Promise hell.
如果你发现自己回到了整个筑巢的事情上，你就错过了重点。
If you find yourself back to the whole nesting thing, you're missing the point.
而你在这里错过的真正的一点是你的回报是你得到的承诺
And the real point that you're missing here is your return a Promise to get
回到原来的链条。
yourself back to the original chain.
在这里，不是为了承诺而锁链，而是将承诺返回到主体
Instead of chaining off for the Promise here return the Promise back to the main
链条并做你的垂直链条，好吗？
chain and do your you're chaining vertically, okay?
所以小心点。
So be careful about that.
很容易就会回到同样的境地
It's very easy to fall back into that same
诱惑是我们一直在做的事情，也就是我习惯把东西嵌套在一起。
temptation is what we've always done which is I'm used to nesting things together.
这是让你自己回到我们所谓的承诺地狱的方法之一。
This is one of the ways you get yourself back into what we call Promise hell.